We, the Se
Super Tough Strong Energy Positive Exciting Soul from Nagoya Team Shach's
Murasaki Purple Kakko kari Yuzuki Ogura and
I am Rine Kitami, From Iginari Tohokusan!
Pleased to meet you!
So, since we are both in charge of purple
We're going to make a nice baked sweet potato.
Yes.
We were working on a project.
We finished toasting them for 15 minutes.
I'm going to turn it over and bake it for another 15 minutes.
Yes, I'm very excited.
Do you smell it?
Not yet... I can't smell it.
I'm over here.
Yes, I know.
Sister, please.
I'd like to grab it.
Looks hot.
Looks hot, be careful
I'll be careful
something like that
Everyone please cheer me on in the comments section
Cheer for us!
Cheer for me!
Looks difficult
Roll around like this, like a cat's paw.
Be careful
Oh, if you do this, it won't be hot at all
Yo, I thought this was for home.
Because I rolled this one.
Hmm...
Why do you think it's going to go this way when it's a marquee cat?
Mononne, yes, it's definitely this way!
I'm sure it's this way.
I think it's this way, but it'll be fine, won't it?
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
I've got it.
I'll take care of it.
I'll stay for 15 minutes.
I'm going to stay for 15 minutes.
While I'm toaster, we'll have a special talk fest.
I've got a subject for you, so I'm going to draw a line in the sand.
I'm going to check it out right before the show.
I'm sure it's different for each of us, but before a show, we check the lyrics...
It may be obvious that we all do it together, but first of all
We would start with "Hayashi", then this song, then this song, and at the end of this song, at this timing, the next song, and why, and so on.
Do you have that?
Well, we started with the whole group and then some of them didn't get it.
If some of the children didn't understand it, it's okay.
It's like, what's next, what's next?
The formation at the end of the song is different at each show.
I'm sitting, I'm sitting, I'm sitting.
But we have to stand for the next song, and so on.
So I hear it takes a lot of time to confirm the details.
Yes, it's true, but during the rehearsal, if it's a new song or a song that hasn't been performed in a while, we have to check the details of the song.
If you had a hard time doing this part of the dance for a new song or a song that hasn't been performed in a while...
If there's a problem with a newer song, you know...
I wonder if she'll be the teacher and we'll all join in.
Speaking of confirming something very last minute, what's the meaning of the next song?
I'll check the meaning of the next song.
Excuse me.
Speaking of things to check right before a gig...
The connection for the next song.
Next song
Okay, excuse me.
Ta-da!
Speaking of mv shoots, it's difficult because we don't have many good mvs.
I can't think of any. We've got a lot of live footage.
I'm sure you're right... but I'm not sure if it's because we're wearing lesson clothes and no set for the song "Date Samba" or what.
Date Samba... the picture behind him is moving so fast...
But they didn't say, "mv, we're filming.
They made us dance one by one without knowing what it was.
Ha-ha-ha-ha
I kinda opened the lid and it turned out to be
Is there any chance that it turned out to be a music video for Date Samba?
No, I don't.
That's funny!
I wonder if it was intentional that you didn't tell us.
Oh, intentionally? Of course it was.
Funny!
But I think it's just barely possible to say it's a certain thing.
Mr. Yumi's mv is in his own clothes.
What?
Private clothes?
And she bought it within her budget.
Wow!
And the songs were styled by me.
But the staff gave me an image of what they wanted to be and what they wanted to be.
The staff gave me an image of what I wanted to be and what I wanted to be.
Wow!
The clothes have a little bit of individuality.
I see.
Clothes have personality.
I tried to bring it out just a little bit.
This is a little off topic, but...
In a song about not losing, the lyrics and the singer are linked emotionally, right?
How did you decide on the lyrics?
You didn't originally choose this lyric because you wanted this girl to sing it, did you?
Oh, I think that's how it was made and assigned.
That's right.
I heard rumors.
Well, we all sang the full song on the recording.
But we'd already been given the recording.
That's right.
It's just that it links to what we're singing.
I'm so glad.
I was really wondering how they decided on that.
I knew it.
That song is great.
It's a pien song, isn't it?
Yeah, it's an emo type song.
It's emo!
I've heard good things about it.
Aru Aru Majibara is like that.
Tohoku Sanchan is so special.
You're right.
Killer whales are pretty normal.
Yeah.
But it's a long day to shoot a music video.
Yes, it is.
So someone will definitely sleep.
Yes, they do.
Okay.
Oh, that's it then?
Yeah, that's it.
Now we're in agreement.
Oh, shit.
What?
Oh, it's a match.
Okay, so...
Is there a rule about music video shoots?
Speaking of music video shoots, someone's going to sleep.
Thank God it came out today.
That's great.
It's been a long day.
Yeah, of course.
All the time, to keep their faces pretty.
You don't sleep during these shoots, right?
I don't sleep.
No, I don't.
Not if it's a half-day shoot.
I sleep because it's a one-day shoot.
So how was the Special Talk Festival?
It was great.
I was able to ask you what I wanted to ask you personally, so it was a very good turnout.
Completed!
It was a lot of fun.
See you tomorrow and next time, we'll be back with you both, so please look forward to it!
That's all for now, Yuzuki Daikoku of Team Shirt and
and Rine Kitami, who is suddenly from Tohoku!
Bye bye!